Andaman, Andaman,
Andaman, Andaman.
Hey, sir!
Sir!
Sir! Sir!
This is considered today's most shocking event.
Actor Anda, who made his debut
in a sensational series,
was found dead inside a private vehicle.
Authorities speculate that
stress from public criticism
may have been a contributing factor
that pushed him over the edge.
[Characters, places and incidents
in this production]
[are entirely fictitious.]
[Viewer discretion is advised.]
[One month earlier]
Podduang.
You're finally awake, Sleeping Beauty.
Or do I have to give you a kiss, too?
What the hell are you playing at?
You're sleeping like there's no tomorrow.
Come on. Get up already.
How did you get in?
What a question.
We were roommates for two years.
In your third year, you moved to a condo.
Did you forget your ex already?
Come on!
What is that sound?
The sound of hunger.
Quick!
[Andaman]
[Fan Club]
[The Field of Love]
[Dorm Mate]
- Smells wonderful.
- Yeah.
I'm starving.
Bum.
What makes you this hungry?
Well, last night,
a guitarist at my brother's place got sick,
so I was called in as a substitute until 3 a.m.
After I got up, Dunk dragged me here.
Why wouldn't I be hungry?
What? We have to make preparations, don't we?
Orientation's almost over. I'm a third-year,
but they still don't know me.
We have to be the mean seniors, right?
We're on the entertainment team.
So feel free to act all tough and cool
in front of the freshmen yourself.
I don't want them to hate me.
They'll surely like me, right, Podduang?
- You're the most handsome.
- Absolutely.
Don't agree with him, Podduang.
Dunk is full of himself.
Which one is better?
Let me see.
- What are you doing?
- This one. This one.
It's about that Anda guy again?
Take that back!
How dare you address him like that?
What? My bad, all right?
Enjoy yourselves, you two. I'll go watch
the soccer highlights while I wait.
I'm so happy.
After two years of waiting,
Anda finally got cast as the lead pair.
Plus, he hits number one
on trending every week.
The agency must've acknowledged his potential.
Yeah, how fabulous.
You hyped up the trend, didn't you?
- Nosy!
- Podduang!
- She said I'm being nosy.
- Well, you are.
- It's absolutely red-hot right now,
- Dunk, louder.
- Anda and James's ship trend...
- Dunk, stop!
What? What exactly do you want me to do?
We're telling you to stop!
- Hello, James, Anda.
- Don't switch the channel just yet.
- Hi.
- Hello, hello.
Is there anything you want to tell the fans
who are waiting for this series?
Anda, you go first.
Let me hold the mic for you.
Well, please look forward to it,
my lovely Andaman fandom.
- Anda is so adorable.
- You're so right.
He's so cute in that look!
- We put so much into this series.
- Yeah, agreed.
Yes, because...
this project has gone through
so much just to get here.
Everyone worked really hard.
He's number one in my book.
Yeah, he's so cute.
- Our first two series were well received.
- Yeah, yeah.
And I hope you're looking forward
to this one as well.
So proud of him. My boy.
Come on. Let's prepare for the orientation.
[Welcome to
the Sports and Health Science Family]
[First Year]
[Ready to Roll]
Are you all having a good time here?
I guess not.
This year, the Faculty of Sports
and Health Science
has the lowest turnout for orientation.
Why is that?
Where are all your friends?
Everyone, stand up!
Hey, quickly!
Pick up the pace if you're one of us!
What I want to tell all of you is this:
We're all brothers and sisters
in this faculty.
We're one big family.
We truly mean it.
This means that
starting right now,
I want everyone
to enjoy this moment with me.
Oh, come on.
You pulled off the act so seamlessly.
How come you couldn't tell?
- My outfit clearly gave it away.
- Dunk, Dunk.
Can I take a video of you? I'm going to shout,
"Why are you wearing a suit, Boss?"
- Do a cool pose, okay?
- All right.
- Yeah, okay.
- Ready?
Three, two, one!
So...
Bum, my beautiful senior,
I want you to be my older sister
in the fraternity.
Should I be happy with the word "older"?
Oh, it was just a joke.
Podduang, can I have your autograph?
Absolutely.
Are you taken?
Wow.
"Are you taken?"
Right? Are you?
Like, is he usually this much of a goofball?
Always. It's his character.
All right. Everyone is here, correct?
Allow me to officially make
this announcement again.
A lot has changed nowadays.
This year's orientation requires
none of the drills
or the usual traditions.
The seniors voted to make orientation
more about getting to know each other.
There's another thing you should know.
This year, there won't be
a Faculty Queen and King,
even though we used to have
our Faculty Queen
and our freaking Faculty King.
I think you two look like a couple.
Is there something going on?
Don't get flustered now.
Should we go back to the old way?
Right, right.
Let's get back on track.
Tomorrow night is the final day of orientation.
We want all of you here at 7 P.M. sharp.
We have something for you.
That's it for today.
[Kensan]
By the way, Podduang, how's your brother?
I heard he attended
the Faculty of Engineering orientation.
Satang didn't.
I think he has to go practice
with the youth squad.
He really is that good.
Don't you feel lonely living alone?
Why? You're asking like
you want to move in or something.
I'd rather not. I'm afraid of heights.
Jeez, you've been with me since freshman year.
This is the first time you've told me.
What? Your old place was only four stories.
Your condo has way more floors.
Dunk, my room is on the third floor.
I know. I was just joking.
There, there.
Gosh, that tickles.
Here. I know it's your favorite.
Excellent. You know me so well.
Oh, Podduang.
Anda's filming for the faculty
this Saturday. Do you want to go?
Of course.
As members of the Andaman fandom,
we can't miss this.
Aren't you afraid to meet your bestie?
Who?
Jinna, obviously.
- Dunk, give it back to me.
- Hey, I was kidding!
- Give it back!
- I was joking.
- Come on!
- No, no. I'm sorry.
Why do you hate him this much?
Come on, Bum.
You forgot it all already?
Jinna and his friends always practiced
on our field when they were freshmen.
They never took care of the place either.
- And that guy always messed with me.
- Right.
Yeah, and he's always a poser.
Jinna or you?
Jinna, of course!
I think it's you.
Hey, what's that?
Look.
Hey!
That's my meatball!
Please, please, please.
Hey!
Hey. You can't have it.
Please.
- Hey!
- It's mine.
Hey, please.
Just one.
This one will do.
I'm stuffed.
How are you getting back to your place?
I think I'm going to walk this way.
Yeah, same.
I'm going to stop by my brother's place first.
What about you?
I've called a ride. It should be here soon.
You two go ahead.
Okay, I'll get going, then.
Yeah, get home safe.
Take care of the bill, okay?
Again, Dunk?
- See you.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Bum.
[Faculty of Engineering]
Oh! I'm sorry.
The path is pretty wide.
Did you do that on purpose?
Who were you talking to?
Never mind.
- Do you know them yet?
- Got any alcohol?
- No, right?
- Introduce me to them.
Oh, it's our Faculty Queen and Faculty King.
- Took you forever.
- Good evening.
- Podduang.
What took you so long?
Right, Golf.
Nice. Nut.
Put your wristband on already. Come on.
- Jeez, I'm about to.
- It's on.
- Come on.
- You don't drink?
I do, but not alcohol.
I know...
you're having an after-party here.
Podduang, I know you've got
the slushy in your cup.
These freshmen know too much.
How about a toast, man?
Not inviting your ship partner to sit with you?
Shit, if Bum hears you say that, you're dead.
Well, you two actually suit each other!
Bum, can you play a song for Dunk?
You're all pushing your luck tonight.
The Queen is coming.
- Things are about to go down.
- I'm scared.
Have a seat here.
This group... is pure trouble.
I'll have Dunk put you all on the soccer team.
Oh, bring it on!
- I'm the real deal. Just watch.
- The real deal.
You see, a newborn's first word is "mama,"
but for us, it's...
- "Goal!"
This batch of freshmen sure loves to brag!
Is it true that engineering students
are your rivals?
Oh, there it is.
What? Why are you looking at me?
It's nothing, really.
When competing in sports,
the two faculties
always trade places between first and second.
So, who's first and who's second?
I'm first, of course!
- Oh, like we'd ever believe that!
- Expect us to buy that?
- For the likes of you--
- Hold on.
I'm your senior here.
Yes, Boss.
- Yes, Boss.
- Wait, wait.
- You're not wearing a suit tonight, Boss?
- Let's stop there.
I'm done with that bit.
Podduang, can you tell us
how the Faculty King and Queen contest went?
Hey, the Faculty King is right here.
Why not just ask him?
Scratch that!
Let's ask the Faculty Queen instead.
Why the hell do you even want to know?
You could've asked something else.
[Faculty of Sports and Health Science]
Are you in this section?
Yes. Are we in the same section?
I'm Podduang.
And I'm Dunk.
What a show-off.
Dunk is my name...
And what's your name?
Bum.
You've got such a weird name.
Why the name "Podduang"?
Podduang was an ancient Thai currency.
Sheesh, that's dope!
I usually hear names like "Pound,"
"Franc," "Euro," and "Dollar."
The classics.
But...
you can just call me "Pod."
No, let's go with "Podduang." Sounds cute.
How about we...
sit together in the class?
Dunk, which bed do you want?
Any. You choose.
I'll go with this one.
Okay.
When will we get rid of
these aggressive orientation traditions?
So fucking boring!
Well...
when you're in your third year,
try to become an aggressive senior yourself.
No way.
Even we gossip about them this much.
When I'm in my third year,
I won't be able to take it.
What?
- Why are you smiling?
- Nothing.
Dunk.
What's the matter?
You can't sleep?
Yeah.
I'll get used to this place soon, I think.
I usually sleep with a bolster.
It's fine.
I have two.
Thank you.
Sweet dreams.
- Good night.
- Let's sleep.
- Andaman!
- This way.
- Come on, come on.
[Shine, Anda]
[Love Anda]
Thank you, thank you.
- Andaman!
Andaman!
- Who's that?
- Oh, that's Anda, a new actor,
and a first-year engineering student.
He's so cute.
Jeez, you're not trying to hide it?
What does it have to do with you?
You're flustered. Podduang, look at her.
Hey!
Look at this.
Am I more handsome than him?
Not at all.
Not true. I'm more handsome.
- Andaman!
- Right. Thank you.
- Andaman.
Those are our Faculty King and Queen!
- You two look so perfect.
- So cute.
Hey.
Doesn't her throat hurt when May yells at us?
Guys. I'm on a date now.
Whoa, with whom?
Golf, a third-year student.
Seriously?
I'm serious.
Hey. Come to think of it,
I think May is pretty cute.
Guys. I broke up with Golf.
Hey, it's okay.
You still have us.
- I'm on a date now.
- Congratulations.
Guys!
He told me I'm too manly for him.
I think he's wrong.
Damn it!
Why does it have to be me?
Burn the bridge. Trust me.
- I'm the one who has no time for him?
- Call it quits.
This guy's the one.
He's adorable!
Congratulations.
I already gave him a black eye.
Great. Leave him.
Guys...
Look.
Look at her pretending to be asleep.
Bum is living her life to the fullest?
Podduang.
Do you find Bum cute?
Are you saying...?
I don't know. Just forget it.
You sleep in my bed.
I'll sleep on the floor tonight.
What are you doing here all alone?
Isn't this the final day
of your faculty orientation?
I just want some peace.
It's loud back there.
And why did you follow me here?
Did I? I was just jogging after practice.
Other people jog here, too.
Can I sit with you?
Your faculty is very lively this year.
It's always been like this.
What's wrong?
You always look so upset.
I'm always like this.
You'd usually smile more.
You say that as if you're always with me.
Well, I do see you from time to time.
I rarely get to see you outside Sports Day.
Yeah.
Even back there,
you bumped into me and ran off.
I almost couldn't remember who it was.
All right, I'm sorry! Is that enough?
I wasn't mad about that.
Hey.
You should apply to be a trainee
at the soccer club.
The team really needs extra hands.
It's your choice.
I just wanted to invite you.
You love seeing Dunk practice, don't you?
Hey, Jinna.
Check the valve clearance
and see if it's 0.15 mm.
Yeah, the valve clearance is too wide.
No wonder it sounded louder
than rock music during the testing.
Tod, are you free?
Help me check other parts.
Hey, you two,
can we do this later?
I'm hungry.
Damn it, Art.
When are you going to work on this if not now?
It won't be just the three of us
in the afternoon once Anda joins.
There'll be, like, dozens more.
It's nice that he'll be here, isn't it?
Don't you miss him or what?
How often do we get to see him in a month?
Though...
I think having a celebrity
as a friend is pretty cool.
All eyes are always on us.
The Communication Arts girls...
Jeez... They weren't looking at you.
They were looking at our friend.
You rat! Want a wrench for breakfast?
Hey, enough already, you two.
You're already fighting at this hour.
Let's grab some food.
- Andaman!
- Andaman.
Andaman.
Thank you.
- You look very handsome in person.
- Thank you very much.
Can you tell the fans watching the livestream
what you and your characters have in common?
Well, we actually have a lot in common.
My character in the series is
wholesome and romantic,
which is kind of like me in real life.
Is it tough to study Engineering?
Can you tell the younger fans
who may want to study here?
I don't think it's hard.
- If I can do well, then so can you.
- Oh, excellent!
And more importantly,
I've got friends helping me.
Art, Jinna, and Tod.
Shit! He's calling us.
- Hello.
- This is Jinna, Tod,
- and Art.
- Hey...
- Anda looks lovely in this outfit.
- Right.
You're all good-looking here.
Can you promote the series for us?
- Absolutely. Please...
- Jinna is pretty handsome, actually.
What? Do you have another bias?
Or maybe it's you.
- Whatever you hate, you will...
- Hate it even more.
- Thank you to the Andaman fandom
- Sure.
for being here today.
The photos are so lovely.
I'm so happy.
Where are you guys from, by the way?
Anda, it's my friend's birthday today.
Happy birthday, Podduang.
I remember you two. Podduang and Bum.
Thanks, Anda. I...
Can I take selfies with you?
- Sure thing.
- Hey, let me join in, too.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
See you around. Oh, thank you.
- Anda...
- Thank you, everyone.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you, thank you.
Right. Thank you.
- Can I take selfies with you?
- Yes, yes.
Thank you!
Please, everyone.
My team and I
have been working really hard on this series.
That's right. We've been working long and hard.
- It's exhausting. How about you?
- It really is.
- This is our third series now.
- Yes.
Thank you. I hope you'll look forward
to this series.
[Home Ekkamai]
Bum, a ton of people are reposting your post.
What's the matter with you two?
It's my birthday, all right?
Enjoy the moment, will you?
- Right.
- Yeah...
- Here.
- Thank you.
Knock yourselves out.
It's on me tonight.
Sure thing.
Right.
Oh, Bum. This is your brother's place.
Sing me a song.
It's not time for the band to perform yet.
Oh, come on.
Jeez...
Come on, Podduang.
You've been smiling since
Anda wished you a happy birthday.
Let's see.
There.
Look at you.
So cute, right?
Is that Jinna?
This is more than just a coincidence.
Should we get him?
- Hey, hey.
- He upset the birthday boy.
No, not yet.
Let's toast.
- That table.
- Me?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday ♪
Want to make a wish first?
I'm Podduang.
And I dunk.
You're finally awake, Sleeping Beauty.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Happy birthday.
- Podduang.
- Hey.
I'm sorry. I really did plan this
with my brother.
But I didn't know that
Jinna was working here tonight.
Take it as a surprise, yeah?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Just having you two already makes me happy.
Right?
Well...
The two of us have something to tell you.
Right. Just say it already.
My present?
- We...
- Where?
Where is it?
- We...
The two of us...
are dating.
Isn't this a surprise?
Yeah, took you two long enough.
It makes me happy
to see both of you finally getting together.
See? I told you he already knew.
A toast.
- Come on, come on.
- Right.
To the Faculty King and Queen,
my dear friends.
Want some?
Go for it. I'm on a diet.
Here, open up.
Come on.
Quick.
Podduang.
Are you all right?
Of course.
What about Dunk?
Is he dead?
Damn it.
You're a lightweight, but you drank a lot.
You can just get him back. I'll...
call a ride myself.
Are you sure you'll be fine?
This is nothing.
Okay, we'll be going now, then.
Get up!
- Getting...
- Come on.
Bye-bye. Oh, oh, come on.
- See you.
- Bye-bye, Podduang.
Bye-bye.
Podduang.
Let go of me.
The place is closed.
Come here.
You're so freaking heavy.
Hey!
Are you all right?
Why do I have to see you everywhere?
I work here.
I'm so sick of you.
Up for another drink? It's on me.
Hey!
How do you get home if you're this drunk?
Go away. I can call a ride just fine.
It's already 3 a.m.
It's almost impossible to find one.
There!
I got it!
Let's go. I'll give you a ride.
None of your business.
I can go home on my own.
Well, I'm the driver.
[Jinna Ronnarak]
What the fuck are you playing at?
Damn it, you...
- What?
- Are you good?
Hop on, kiddo.
You're the passenger. I'm driving.
I need to wear the jacket first.
I'm using mobile pay.
You're pretty heavy, you know?
Did you call me fat?
Podduang.
You're home.
You sure you'll be fine?
Podduang!
Thank you!
The helmet.
Podduang!
Here's the change.
Your tip, kiddo.
How did I get home?
The faculty announced that
tryouts for first-years are starting
for certain sports,
which is why we're all gathered here.
This year,
tryouts for soccer, basketball,
volleyball, and badminton
will be held in this gym.
We'd like to thank all the freshmen
and sophomores for showing interest.
For each session, the third-year students
will be here to mentor you.
Put your names in the sports
you're interested in.
Lots of students?
Yeah, there are so many students here.
- How are you doing?
- Hungover, obviously.
Let's not get drunk like that anymore.
Dunk puked his guts out, too.
Why did you have to get that drunk?
Well, it's your birthday.
Next year, I'll get to host your birthday party
alongside our anniversary. On the same day.
- How did you get home last night, though?
- Well...
Just the usual way.
We're sorry for having to leave early.
I had a deadweight to deal with.
What?
And how are the tryouts?
Things are looking good for us this year.
A lot more students showed up than last year.
I hope that for this year's university games,
athletes from our faculty
make it onto the varsity team.
- Yeah.
- Definitely.
The Engineering students always steal our spot.
True.
- Oh?
- Hey.
Dunk, the coach said we have to practice here.
How come?
This is our faculty's gym.
Go practice at your gym.
Read this first before getting mad at me.
"Under maintenance."
Then practice at the soccer field.
Why, are you scared?
Scared of what?
Scared of the issues
your faculty's had in past years.
How about we ignore this paper, then?
Whichever faculty wins
takes the gym for the entire week.
Deal.
Podduang.
Podduang!
[Score 06-05]
Close, wasn't it?
Yeah, we made the deal.
This means I'll get to see you more often?
- We're set. Finally, a place to practice.
- Sweet.
I've been feeling a bit uneasy lately, Jinna.
What? You're struggling
to live a life as a celebrity?
Look at this.
[Go to hell]
Shit.
From whom?
Not sure.
I've received a ton of gifts, too.
There's only this one with this type of note.
Sure it wasn't sent to the wrong address?
What's going on, Anda?
Well...
I've received a threat.
Anyway, be careful for now, Anda.
This clearly was sent with bad intentions.
Podduang.
Are you all right?
Which floor?
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
You're so freaking heavy.
Podduang.
Are you awake?
Yes, baby?
Wake up. You're home.
Podduang!
He's really out cold?
Jinna...
Got a crush on me?
No, not that.
Podduang, I feel like
I'm hurting your feelings right now.
I've already got someone I like.
Seriously,
when did you and Jinna start talking?
Why? You're worried about your friend?
And what's wrong, Podduang?
It's about my internship hours
with the core team.
I still don't know which team I should join.
I told you to join the soccer team with me.
Why complicate things?
You came. At this rate, who's actually
following whom, I wonder?